(Sheldon:)in these tuxedo pants.
(Stuart:)So, I met Jeanie
at your Aunt Gladys'.
(Stuart:)She passed me
the Manischewitz,
(Stuart:)I took one look
at this punim,
(Stuart:)and I almost plotzed
on the kugel.
(Rajj:)Is this what I sound like
when I talk about India?
(Howard:)So, my mother's okay
with this?
(Jeannie:)Why would your mother have
a problem with me and Stuart?
'Cause they have a weird,
inappropriate relationship.
(Jeannie:)Weirder than what you and I
did in my dad's Corolla?
(Raj:)This is so messed up.
(Emily:)I know, I'm having
the best time.
(Howard:)Why would you even come to this?
(Howard:)Didn't you know I'd be here?
(Jeannie:)It was a long
time ago, Howard.
(Stuart:)And you're only second
cousins, who cares?
(Bernadette:)So, you knew and you
brought her anyway?
(Stuart:)Oh, so she's good enough
for Howard, but not for me?!
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, go have weird
relationships
(Bernadette:)with your own
mother and cousin.
(Bernadette:)This is his turf.
(Howard:)Yeah.